{
  "qas": [
    {"key": "India", "question": "India", "answer": "ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡³"},
    {"key": "China", "question": "China", "answer": "ğŸ‡¨ğŸ‡³"},
    {"key": "USA", "question": "USA", "answer": "ğŸ‡ºğŸ‡¸"},
    {"key": "Japan", "question": "Japan", "answer": "ğŸ‡¯ğŸ‡µ"},
    {"key": "France", "question": "France", "answer": "ğŸ‡«ğŸ‡·"},
    {"key": "Germany", "question": "Germany", "answer": "ğŸ‡©ğŸ‡ª"},
    {"key": "Italy", "question": "Italy", "answer": "ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹"},
    {"key": "Brazil", "question": "Brazil", "answer": "ğŸ‡§ğŸ‡·"},
    {"key": "Niger", "question": "Niger", "answer": "ğŸ‡³ğŸ‡ª"},
    {"key": "UK", "question": "UK", "answer": "ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§"},
    {"key": "Australia", "question": "Australia", "answer": "ğŸ‡¦ğŸ‡º"},
    {"key": "Russia", "question": "Russia", "answer": "ğŸ‡·ğŸ‡º"},
    {"key": "Spain", "question": "Spain", "answer": "ğŸ‡ªğŸ‡¸"},
    {"key": "Mexico", "question": "Mexico", "answer": "ğŸ‡²ğŸ‡½"},
    {"key": "South Korea", "question": "South Korea", "answer": "ğŸ‡°ğŸ‡·"},
    {"key": "South Africa", "question": "South Africa", "answer": "ğŸ‡¿ğŸ‡¦"}
  ],

  "innerOrder": [
    "India","China","USA","Japan",
    "France","Germany","Italy","Brazil",
    "Niger","UK","Australia","Russia",
    "Spain","Mexico","South Korea","South Africa"
  ],

  "printOrder": [
    "India","China","USA","Japan",
    "France","Germany","Italy","Brazil",
    "Niger","UK","Australia","Russia",
    "Spain","Mexico","South Korea","South Africa"
  ],

  "outerFlags": [
    "ğŸ‡»ğŸ‡³","ğŸ‡±ğŸ‡·","ğŸ‡·ğŸ‡º",
    "ğŸ‡«ğŸ‡·","ğŸ‡²ğŸ‡½","ğŸ‡°ğŸ‡·",
    "ğŸ‡¯ğŸ‡²","ğŸ‡³ğŸ‡ª","ğŸ‡¨ğŸ‡³",
    "ğŸ‡¦ğŸ‡º","ğŸ‡µğŸ‡±","ğŸ‡·ğŸ‡´",
    "ğŸ‡©ğŸ‡ª","ğŸ‡ºğŸ‡¬","ğŸ‡¿ğŸ‡¦",
    "ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡³","ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§","ğŸ‡ºğŸ‡¸",
    "ğŸ‡¯ğŸ‡µ","ğŸ‡ªğŸ‡¸","ğŸ‡§ğŸ‡ª",
    "ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹","ğŸ‡§ğŸ‡·","ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡ª"
  ]
}
